liquorstoreclothing.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy

In this privacy policy, the terms “we”, “our” and “us” are used to refer to Liquor Store. It will outline how Liquor Store will collect, use, store and share your personal data.

Our customers are the heart of Liquor Store and we strive above everything to ensure customer satisfaction. We take our customers privacy and security very seriously and we are committed to protecting your data so that you can shop with us without any worries. Please read our policy carefully and if you have any questions or should you wish to contact us about the use of your data, don’t hesitate to ask. Email [sales@liquorstoreclothing.com](mailto:sales@liquorstoreclothing.com) or call 0121 2365830

**What** **I** **nformation** **D** **o** **W** **e** **C** **ollect?**

If you have an account with us or you make a purchase online, we collect your name and contact details including your billing address, email address, telephone number and details about your order. 

Other ways that we collect information are:

\- Customer’s name and email address when using our email contact form 

\- Customer’s name and email address when subscribing to our newsletter both in-store and online

\- Customer’s name and email address when entering a competiton or giveaway

\- Customer’s name and address when sending store bought items by post 

\- Customer’ s name and telephone/email to contact them as notification that their item is available for collection 

We also have CCTV monitoring equipment in our store.

The above stated information is collected in order to provide you with the services you have selected for the legitimate interests of our business.

### **Data Integrity and Security**

We do not, and will not, sell any of your information to any third party, including your name, address, email address or credit card information. We will only disclose this information to a third party  where it is necessary for them to provide us with the services we need or if there is a legal obligation to do so. 

Data is only used for the purposes stated above whilst you continue to engage with us. Should you cease to engage with us for a period of five years, your data will be suppressed and you will cease to receive communications from us. 

Transmission of information via the internet is not and cannot be completely secure. We will do our utmost to protect your personal data, however we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our website. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. This being said, please be aware that any transmission of data is at your own risk. 

**Your** **R** **ights in** **R** **elation to** **P** **ersonal** **D** **ata**

You have the right to withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data at any time by emailing [sales@liquorstoreclothing.com](mailto:sales@liquorstoreclothing.com) or call 0121 2365830. Please use said contact details to lodge a complaint, to access your personal information or for the correction and deletion of data.  

We will communicate any changes to this privacy policy to you and any updated privacy policies will appear on this page.

This policy was last reviewed and updated in May 2018.
